[{"date": "2018-12-26 22:53:46.663998", "answer": "\ufeffOk, in Ordnung", "difficulty": 1, "info1": "", "chunk": 0, "info2": "", "question": "\uad1c\ucc2e\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-26 22:53:46.664037", "answer": "w\u00fctend", "difficulty": 1, "info1": "", "chunk": 0, "info2": "", "question": "\ud654\ub098\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-26 22:53:46.664050", "answer": "ver\u00e4rgert, w\u00fctend", "difficulty": 1, "info1": "", "chunk": 0, "info2": "", "question": "\uc9dc\uc99d\ub098\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-26 22:53:46.664059", "answer": "schlecht", "difficulty": 1, "info1": "", "chunk": 0, "info2": "", "question": "\ub098\uc058\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-26 22:53:46.664068", "answer": "sch\u00f6n", "difficulty": 1, "info1": "", "chunk": 0, "info2": "", "question": "\uc544\ub984\ub2f5\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-26 22:53:46.664076", "answer": "gro\u00df", "difficulty": 1, "info1": "", "chunk": 0, "info2": "", "question": "\ud06c\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-26 22:53:46.664084", "answer": "bitter", "difficulty": 1, "info1": "", "chunk": 0, "info2": "", "question": "\uc4f0\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-26 22:53:46.664093", "answer": "langweilig", "difficulty": 1, "info1": "", "chunk": 0, "info2": "", "question": "\uc2ec\uc2ec\ud558\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-26 22:53:46.664102", "answer": "langweilig", "difficulty": 1, "info1": "", "chunk": 0, "info2": "", "question": "\uc9c0\ub8e8\ud558\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-26 22:53:46.664110", "answer": "mutig", "difficulty": 1, "info1": "", "chunk": 0, "info2": "", "question": "\uc529\uc529\ud558\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-26 22:53:46.664118", "answer": "billig", "difficulty": 1, "info1": "", "chunk": 1, "info2": "", "question": "\uc2f8\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-26 22:53:46.664127", "answer": "k\u00fchl", "difficulty": 1, "info1": "", "chunk": 1, "info2": "", "question": "\uc2f8\ub298\ud558\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-26 22:53:46.664135", "answer": "mollig, dick", "difficulty": 1, "info1": "", "chunk": 1, "info2": "", "question": "\ud1b5\ud1b5\ud558\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-26 22:53:46.664143", "answer": "sauber", "difficulty": 1, "info1": "", "chunk": 1, "info2": "", "question": "\uae68\ub057\ud558\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-26 22:53:46.664151", "answer": "wolkig", "difficulty": 1, "info1": "", "chunk": 1, "info2": "", "question": "\ud750\ub9ac\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-26 22:53:46.664159", "answer": "kalt", "difficulty": 1, "info1": "", "chunk": 1, "info2": "", "question": "\ucda5\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-26 22:53:46.664168", "answer": "kalt", "difficulty": 1, "info1": "", "chunk": 1, "info2": "", "question": "\ucc28\uac11\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-26 22:53:46.664177", "answer": "angenehm, bequem", "difficulty": 1, "info1": "", "chunk": 1, "info2": "", "question": "\ud3b8\ud558\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-26 22:53:46.664186", "answer": "praktisch", "difficulty": 1, "info1": "", "chunk": 1, "info2": "", "question": "\ud3b8\ub9ac\ud558\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-26 22:53:46.664194", "answer": "erfrischend, k\u00fchl", "difficulty": 1, "info1": "", "chunk": 1, "info2": "", "question": "\uc2dc\uc6d0\ud558\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-26 22:53:46.664203", "answer": "s\u00fc\u00df", "difficulty": 1, "info1": "", "chunk": 2, "info2": "", "question": "\uadc0\uc5fd\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-26 22:53:46.664211", "answer": "nass, feucht", "difficulty": 1, "info1": "", "chunk": 2, "info2": "", "question": "\ucd95\ucd95\ud558\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-26 22:53:46.664220", "answer": "schw\u00fcl", "difficulty": 1, "info1": "", "chunk": 2, "info2": "", "question": "\uc2b5\ud558\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-26 22:53:46.664228", "answer": "lecker", "difficulty": 1, "info1": "", "chunk": 2, "info2": "", "question": "\ub9db\uc788\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-26 22:53:46.664240", "answer": "anders", "difficulty": 1, "info1": "", "chunk": 2, "info2": "", "question": "\ub2e4\ub974\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-26 22:53:46.664250", "answer": "schwierig, schwer", "difficulty": 1, "info1": "", "chunk": 2, "info2": "", "question": "\uc5b4\ub835\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-26 22:53:46.664258", "answer": "dreckig", "difficulty": 1, "info1": "", "chunk": 2, "info2": "", "question": "\ub354\ub7fd\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-26 22:53:46.664267", "answer": "trocken", "difficulty": 1, "info1": "", "chunk": 2, "info2": "", "question": "\uac74\uc870\ud558\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-26 22:53:46.664275", "answer": "fr\u00fch", "difficulty": 1, "info1": "", "chunk": 2, "info2": "", "question": "\uc774\ub974\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-26 22:53:46.664283", "answer": "leicht", "difficulty": 1, "info1": "", "chunk": 2, "info2": "", "question": "\uc27d\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-26 22:53:46.664292", "answer": "peinlich", "difficulty": 1, "info1": "", "chunk": 3, "info2": "", "question": "\ub2f9\ud669\ud558\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-26 22:53:46.664300", "answer": "leer", "difficulty": 1, "info1": "", "chunk": 3, "info2": "", "question": "\ube44\uc5b4 \uc788\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-26 22:53:46.664308", "answer": "teuer", "difficulty": 1, "info1": "", "chunk": 3, "info2": "", "question": "\ube44\uc2f8\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-26 22:53:46.664316", "answer": "schnell", "difficulty": 1, "info1": "", "chunk": 3, "info2": "", "question": "\ube60\ub974\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-26 22:53:46.664327", "answer": "dick", "difficulty": 1, "info1": "", "chunk": 3, "info2": "", "question": "\ub6b1\ub6b1\ud558\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-26 22:53:46.664336", "answer": "fettig", "difficulty": 1, "info1": "", "chunk": 3, "info2": "", "question": "\uae30\ub984\uc9c0\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-26 22:53:46.664344", "answer": "wenig", "difficulty": 1, "info1": "", "chunk": 3, "info2": "", "question": "\uc801\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-26 22:53:46.664353", "answer": "frisch", "difficulty": 1, "info1": "", "chunk": 3, "info2": "", "question": "\uc2e0\uc120\ud558\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-26 22:53:46.664363", "answer": "voll", "difficulty": 1, "info1": "", "chunk": 3, "info2": "", "question": "\uac00\ub4dd\ud558\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-26 22:53:46.664371", "answer": "nass", "difficulty": 1, "info1": "", "chunk": 3, "info2": "", "question": "\uc816\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-26 22:53:46.664380", "answer": "gl\u00fccklich, fr\u00f6hlich", "difficulty": 1, "info1": "", "chunk": 4, "info2": "", "question": "\uae30\uc058\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-26 22:53:46.664389", "answer": "gut aussehend", "difficulty": 1, "info1": "", "chunk": 4, "info2": "", "question": "\uc798\uc0dd\uae30\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-26 22:53:46.664397", "answer": "nett", "difficulty": 1, "info1": "", "chunk": 4, "info2": "", "question": "\ucc29\ud558\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-26 22:53:46.664407", "answer": "gut", "difficulty": 1, "info1": "", "chunk": 4, "info2": "", "question": "\uc88b\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-26 22:53:46.664416", "answer": "gl\u00fccklich, fr\u00f6hlich", "difficulty": 1, "info1": "", "chunk": 4, "info2": "", "question": "\ud589\ubcf5\ud558\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-26 22:53:46.664424", "answer": "steif, hart", "difficulty": 1, "info1": "", "chunk": 4, "info2": "", "question": "\ub531\ub531\ud558\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-26 22:53:46.664433", "answer": "gesund", "difficulty": 1, "info1": "", "chunk": 4, "info2": "", "question": "\uac74\uac15\ud558\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-26 22:53:46.664441", "answer": "hoch", "difficulty": 1, "info1": "", "chunk": 4, "info2": "", "question": "\ub192\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-26 22:53:46.664449", "answer": "hei\u00df", "difficulty": 1, "info1": "", "chunk": 4, "info2": "", "question": "\ub728\uac81\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-26 22:53:46.664457", "answer": "hei\u00df, warm", "difficulty": 1, "info1": "", "chunk": 4, "info2": "", "question": "\ub365\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-26 22:53:46.664470", "answer": "hungrig", "difficulty": 1, "info1": "", "chunk": 5, "info2": "", "question": "\ubc30\uac00 \uace0\ud504\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-26 22:53:46.664479", "answer": "unangenehm, unbequem", "difficulty": 1, "info1": "", "chunk": 5, "info2": "", "question": "\ubd88\ud3b8\ud558\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-26 22:53:46.664490", "answer": "interessant", "difficulty": 1, "info1": "", "chunk": 5, "info2": "", "question": "\uc7ac\ubbf8\uc788\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-26 22:53:46.664499", "answer": "kompliziert", "difficulty": 1, "info1": "", "chunk": 5, "info2": "", "question": "\ubcf5\uc7a1\ud558\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-26 22:53:46.664507", "answer": "sp\u00e4t", "difficulty": 1, "info1": "", "chunk": 5, "info2": "", "question": "\ub2a6\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-26 22:53:46.664517", "answer": "wenig", "difficulty": 1, "info1": "", "chunk": 5, "info2": "", "question": "\uc801\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-26 22:53:46.664526", "answer": "viel", "difficulty": 1, "info1": "", "chunk": 5, "info2": "", "question": "\ub9ce\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-26 22:53:46.664534", "answer": "laut", "difficulty": 1, "info1": "", "chunk": 5, "info2": "", "question": "\uc2dc\ub044\ub7fd\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-26 22:53:46.664543", "answer": "gemein", "difficulty": 1, "info1": "", "chunk": 5, "info2": "", "question": "\ube44\uc5f4\ud558\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-26 22:53:46.664551", "answer": "feucht", "difficulty": 1, "info1": "", "chunk": 5, "info2": "", "question": "\ucd09\ucd09\ud558\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-26 22:53:46.664560", "answer": "eng", "difficulty": 1, "info1": "", "chunk": 6, "info2": "", "question": "\uc881\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-26 22:53:46.664568", "answer": "neu", "difficulty": 1, "info1": "", "chunk": 6, "info2": "", "question": "\uc0c8\ub86d\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-26 22:53:46.664579", "answer": "uninteressant, langweilig", "difficulty": 1, "info1": "", "chunk": 6, "info2": "", "question": "\uc7ac\ubbf8\uc5c6\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-26 22:53:46.664593", "answer": "nicht lecker, geschmacklos", "difficulty": 1, "info1": "", "chunk": 6, "info2": "", "question": "\ub9db\uc5c6\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-26 22:53:46.664601", "answer": "alt", "difficulty": 1, "info1": "", "chunk": 6, "info2": "", "question": "\uc624\ub798\ub418\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-26 22:53:46.664610", "answer": "sch\u00f6n, h\u00fcbsch", "difficulty": 1, "info1": "", "chunk": 6, "info2": "", "question": "\uc608\uc058\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-26 22:53:46.664620", "answer": "leise", "difficulty": 1, "info1": "", "chunk": 6, "info2": "", "question": "\uc870\uc6a9\ud558\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-26 22:53:46.664628", "answer": "traurig", "difficulty": 1, "info1": "", "chunk": 6, "info2": "", "question": "\uc2ac\ud504\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-26 22:53:46.664636", "answer": "salzig", "difficulty": 1, "info1": "", "chunk": 6, "info2": "", "question": "\uc9dc\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-26 22:53:46.664645", "answer": "unheimlich", "difficulty": 1, "info1": "", "chunk": 6, "info2": "", "question": "\ubb34\uc12d\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-26 22:53:46.664653", "answer": "scharf, spitz", "difficulty": 1, "info1": "", "chunk": 7, "info2": "", "question": "\ub0a0\uce74\ub86d\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-26 22:53:46.664661", "answer": "sch\u00fcchtern", "difficulty": 1, "info1": "", "chunk": 7, "info2": "", "question": "\uc218\uc90d\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-26 22:53:46.664672", "answer": "krank, schmerzhaf", "difficulty": 1, "info1": "", "chunk": 7, "info2": "", "question": "\uc544\ud504\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-26 22:53:46.664681", "answer": "\u00e4hnlich", "difficulty": 1, "info1": "", "chunk": 7, "info2": "", "question": "\ube44\uc2b7\ud558\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-26 22:53:46.664689", "answer": "d\u00fcnn, d\u00fcrr", "difficulty": 1, "info1": "", "chunk": 7, "info2": "", "question": "\uae61\ub9c8\ub974\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-26 22:53:46.664697", "answer": "m\u00fcde, schl\u00e4frig", "difficulty": 1, "info1": "", "chunk": 7, "info2": "", "question": "\uc878\ub9ac\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-26 22:53:46.664705", "answer": "schlank", "difficulty": 1, "info1": "", "chunk": 7, "info2": "", "question": "\ub0a0\uc52c\ud558\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-26 22:53:46.664714", "answer": "rutschig", "difficulty": 1, "info1": "", "chunk": 7, "info2": "", "question": "\ubbf8\ub044\ub7fd\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-26 22:53:46.664722", "answer": "langsam", "difficulty": 1, "info1": "", "chunk": 7, "info2": "", "question": "\ub290\ub9ac\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-26 22:53:46.664730", "answer": "klein", "difficulty": 1, "info1": "", "chunk": 7, "info2": "", "question": "\uc791\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-26 22:53:46.664740", "answer": "klug, smart", "difficulty": 1, "info1": "", "chunk": 8, "info2": "", "question": "\ub611\ub611\ud558\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-26 22:53:46.664751", "answer": "weich", "difficulty": 1, "info1": "", "chunk": 8, "info2": "", "question": "\ubd80\ub4dc\ub7fd\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-26 22:53:46.664759", "answer": "weich", "difficulty": 1, "info1": "", "chunk": 8, "info2": "", "question": "\ub9d0\ub791\ud558\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-26 22:53:46.664768", "answer": "sauer", "difficulty": 1, "info1": "", "chunk": 8, "info2": "", "question": "\uc2dc\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-26 22:53:46.664776", "answer": "scharf", "difficulty": 1, "info1": "", "chunk": 8, "info2": "", "question": "\ub9f5\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-26 22:53:46.664784", "answer": "stark", "difficulty": 1, "info1": "", "chunk": 8, "info2": "", "question": "\uac15\ud558\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-26 22:53:46.664796", "answer": "dumm, d\u00e4mlich", "difficulty": 1, "info1": "", "chunk": 8, "info2": "", "question": "\uba4d\uccad\ud558\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-26 22:53:46.664804", "answer": "\u00fcberrascht", "difficulty": 1, "info1": "", "chunk": 8, "info2": "", "question": "\ub180\ub77c\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-26 22:53:46.664813", "answer": "s\u00fc\u00df", "difficulty": 1, "info1": "", "chunk": 8, "info2": "", "question": "\ub2ec\ub2e4, \ub2ec\ucf64\ud558\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-26 22:53:46.664821", "answer": "gleich", "difficulty": 1, "info1": "", "chunk": 8, "info2": "", "question": "\uac19\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-26 22:53:46.664832", "answer": "durstig", "difficulty": 1, "info1": "", "chunk": 9, "info2": "", "question": "\ubaa9\uc774 \ub9c8\ub974\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-26 22:53:46.664840", "answer": "m\u00fcde", "difficulty": 1, "info1": "", "chunk": 9, "info2": "", "question": "\ud53c\uace4\ud558\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-26 22:53:46.664849", "answer": "h\u00e4\u00dflig, nicht sch\u00f6n", "difficulty": 1, "info1": "", "chunk": 9, "info2": "", "question": "\ubabb\uc0dd\uae30\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-26 22:53:46.664857", "answer": "unangenehm, unbequem", "difficulty": 1, "info1": "", "chunk": 9, "info2": "", "question": "\ubd88\ud3b8\ud558\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-26 22:53:46.664869", "answer": "eilig", "difficulty": 1, "info1": "", "chunk": 9, "info2": "", "question": "\uae09\ud558\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-26 22:53:46.664877", "answer": "warm", "difficulty": 1, "info1": "", "chunk": 9, "info2": "", "question": "\ub530\ub73b\ud558\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-26 22:53:46.664886", "answer": "schwach", "difficulty": 1, "info1": "", "chunk": 9, "info2": "", "question": "\uc57d\ud558\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-26 22:53:46.664894", "answer": "komisch", "difficulty": 1, "info1": "", "chunk": 9, "info2": "", "question": "\uc774\uc0c1\ud558\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-26 22:53:46.664902", "answer": "weit, breit", "difficulty": 1, "info1": "", "chunk": 9, "info2": "", "question": "\ub113\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-26 22:53:46.664911", "answer": "satt", "difficulty": 1, "info1": "", "chunk": 9, "info2": "", "question": "\ubc30\ubd80\ub974\ub2e4", "learned": false}]